

Leadership Advisor, Trainer, & Coach





Objective

Be an outstanding Leader of the Co-Active Leadership Program within The Coaches Training Institute, committed to be and do whatever it takes to empower Global Co-Active Leaders to create a world of love, peace, and abundance by leading the tribes growing experience both in Spanish & English.



Why?

To be fulfilled, to show my love and care for people, to give back, to support people experiencing and benefitting from the life transformation I experienced through the CTI leadership program and to contribute to expand exponentially their impact in the world.



Qualifications

- Raving fan, hungry learner and connoisseur of the Co-Active model, mission, environment, and services
- o Graduate of CTI Leadership Program & Certified Professional Coactive Coach in a record time of 14 months since starting the coaching core curriculum (April 2011 June 2012)
- PSYCH-K® advanced facilitator
- o Usui and Karuna Reiki Master & Qi Gong learner
- Passionate advocate of experiential learning & professional lecturer



Leadership Advisor, Trainer, & Coach





Experience

Current (2011-...)

Owner of JorgeSerrano.com, 9 months

- + Maintaining and Developing a regular coaching practice with life coaching in person and by phone/skype (approx. 120 hours experience in coaching)
- + Leading workshops of coaching skills for teachers and university professors
- + Disseminating the benefits of coaching through public speaking and live demonstrations in Spain
- + Developing my leadership skills through continuous engagements in training programs, both as participant and as assistant (Psycho-drama, 5 Rithms dance, ...)
- + Organizing events to enhance Personal Leadership for other facilitators / instructors (e.g. PSYCH-K® workshops)

2008-2011

Researcher and Assistant Professor in Physics, 4 years

- + Organizing international conferences and workshops
- + Public speaking at international and national conferences
- + Advising a graduate student in Materials Science
- + Applying for grants and leading research projects with international funds
- + Disseminating scientific results through publication in peerreviewed specialized journals (more than 50 articles since 1999, with more than 700 citations)



Leadership Advisor, Trainer, & Coach



2003-2008

Research Associate, Paris and Grenoble (France), 4 years

- + Serving to the scientific community as technical advisor in a multinational research center
- + Developing grant application skills
- + Learning and becoming fluent in French

1999-2003

Ph.D. student - Researcher in Semiconductor Physics, Stuttgart (Germany), 4 years

- + Developing and focusing curiosity into research skills
- + Developing soft skills while working in an international environment
- + Becoming fluent in English and German



Education

2012

CTI Leadership Program (Sitges, Spain, graduated in June 1st, STAGS Tribe)

CTI Co-Active Certification Program (graduated in April 18th, ATENEA Pod)

CTI Bridging the gap to the new Co-Active Model (Madrid, Spain)

5 Rithms - Initiation Workshop (Barcelona, Spain)

Psycho-drama - Initiation Workshop (Madrid, Spain)

2011

Numerology I (Barcelona, Spain)

CTI Co-Active Coaching Core Curriculum (Barcelona, Spain)



Leadership Advisor, Trainer, & Coach



Anthony Robbins Company(ARC): Life and Wealth Mastery (Palm Springs)

2010

PSYCH-K ® Advanced Workshop (Barcelona, Spain) Accelerated Learning Strategies (Barcelona, Spain)

2009

PSYCH-K® Basic Workshop (Barcelona, Spain) Karuna Reiki Mastery (Madrid, Spain)

2005

Usui Reiki III & Usui Reiki Mastery (Madrid, Spain)

2004

Usui Reiki I & II (Madrid, Spain) Qi Gong Practitioner (Stuttgart, Germany) ARC Wealth Mastery (London, U.K.)

2003

ARC Date With Destiny (DWD) (Bahamas)
ARC Unleash the Power Within you (UPW) (Frankfurt, Germany)
Ph.D. in Sciences (Max Planck Society, Stuttgart, Germany)

1998

M.Sc. in Physics: Award to best M.Sc. in Physics at University of Valladolid, Spain

1997

B.Sc. in Physics, University of Valladolid, Spain. Graduated with honors.



Leadership Advisor, Trainer, & Coach





Personal

I live in Valladolid, Spain, with my daughter Sofía. I discovered personal leadership programs through Anthony Robbin's live event (UPW) in Frankfurt in 2003. It was such an amazing experience for me that I then enrolled to Mastery University.

In Dec. 2004 I participated in Date with Destiny, Robbin's cutting edge program on transforming psychology, which turned into changing completely my values and attitude towards life, with a determination to find my soul mate and an immense desire to contribute with the skills and knowledge I acquired there to transform education at an early stage.

Two months later I fell into a depression and it took me nearly 6 months to recover. I met then my soul mate, Sandra, and we enjoyed living together until January 2011, when she passed away due to a stomach cancer. This blow made me realize how short span life can be, and I determined to take a leave from the academic world and develop my passion for coaching. Supporting my wife during her last years has brought me a lot of compassion, love, and wisdom that I now use to better serve my family, friends, colleagues, and clients.

Thanks to both a Co-Active and a Robbin's Result Coach and a previous experience with co-active coaching, I enrolled in CTI coaching core curriculum. Thrilled with the experience of experimenting co-activity and observing co-leading, I decided to continue my training with CTI certification & leadership programs.







Simultaneously to this training process, I started developing a probono coaching practice in my former high school by training teachers in the co-active model and offering them supervision and Q&A sessions on a monthly basis to deepen their learning and support them in the application of the concepts in the class. This has been an amazing experience which led me to focus my leader quest in developing leadership & excellence in education in a co-active way, i.e. with state-of-the-art training methods and way of being.

I love traveling, connecting people and with people, understanding their life, their needs and help them the best I can. I love healthy food, sports such as jogging, running, and swimming, meditation, reading.

I am definitely a team player who also enjoys taking leading roles, creative, and passionate about life, growth, and service.

I enjoy speaking different languages: I am fluent in Spanish, English, German and French, and I have a goal to become fluent in Arab and Chinese by 2016.



Summary

I am a loving, passionate, and excellence-driven trainer & coach, enthusiastic about the Co-Active models, training, and services, who has demonstrated outstanding coaching skills both in Spanish, English, and German.

My greatest assets as person are love and care for people, compassion, and the ability to create a sacred relation with nearly every person. As a leader, I am gifted with an impressive intuition, channeling ability &







spiritual connection, that I put at the service of my community, both in personal and in professional life, leading both in front of the room and behind the scenes.

I have failed many times. I have overcome many challenges. My curiosity, strive to grow, and persistence, have made me learn a lot from challenges and failures that have empowered me to contribute with my experience and learning to help others. It is time for me to give back what I got from CTI and from other leadership trainings, and I feel confident of being an extraordinary asset for the CTI Leadership Faculty.

I look forward to working within the Coaches Training Institute.



Recommendation letters

Please, find attached two recommendation letters to this application as Leader of the CTI Leadership Program.



Lisbon, June 25th 2012

Object: Jorge Serrano's Application for Leader of CTI Leadership Program

To whom it may concern,

My name is Jorge Coutinho and I am a senior leader trained by Anthony Robbins. I was serving Jorge Serrano as a Results Coach within Robbins Research Institute over six months.

Jorge's passion for growth and leadership brought the game to a whole new level. Every session Jorge was coming with results achieved and wanting more. He played full out and was able to bring the best of him to the table. He is a committed and servant Coach & Leader, he loves people, speaks fluently Spanish (his native language) and English and has a worked with people for whole is life. I truly believe that Jorge will be an asset for the Leadership Program Department of the Coaches Training Institute.

For any further information to support his application to Leader of the CTI Leadership Program, please feel free to contact me by email at jorgec@tonyrobbins.com

Sincerely,



BeCoach, Lda.

- > Au. República, 6 7º Esq.
- > 1050-191 Lisboa
- > telefone... +351213 303 760
- > fax.....+351 213 303 733

e-mail.....info@becoach.pt www.becoach.pt

Our passion, your success.

Coach Active

CPCC, MCC, MCIL יוסי אילות מאמן אישי עסקי מוסמך

Yossi Eilot

Master Certified Coach

Recommendation for Jorge Serrano's application to CTI Leadership Program LeaderTo Whom It May Concern,

I am writing this recommendation on behalf of Jorge Serrano. I had the privilege to work with Jorge during his training as co-active coach and co-active leader, and to coach and watch him grow both as a person and as a leader for the last year. Jorge is a loving soul and a passionate person with an immense desire to contribute to the world. He has shown his heart and talent for coaching and leadership since the early stages of his training as co-active coach. His insights and sharings were then of great value to his group, and I would like to highlight his commitment to learn and grow, both for himself as for the sake of his team and clients. Jorge is definitely an outstanding teamplayer and leader who enjoys being curious about, caring, and connecting with people to better serve them. He has surmounted many challenges in life, demonstrating will, tenacity and perseverance in his endeavors. His extraordinary intuition, heart, and curiosity will benefit enormously the participants of the CTI Leadership Program, if you decide to hire him as a Program Leader.

Jorge has the ability to speak Spanish, English, German and French with fluency, and a drive to learn other languages which makes him an ideal candidate for a multilingual-multicultural service, fitting the expansion process that CTI Leadership Program is undergoing. His experience living in Germany, France and Spain, and his former career as researcher in international centers gives him an impressive understanding and caring for multicultural differences.

I am convinced that Jorge would be an excellent asset to the CTI faculty, and I encourage you to hire him as a Leadership Program Leader.

Warm regards,

Yossi

Yossi Eilot, CPCC, MCC, MCIL Master Certified Co-Active Coach CTI Faculty member 972(50)227- 8555 eiloty1@bezeqint.com www.CTI-Israel.com B.P. 580 71799 Makabim ISRAEL

> Cell: +972-50-2278555, Tel: +972-77-7000720 <u>Eiloty1@bezegint.net</u>